interface FaqItem {
    question: string
    answer: string
}

export const servicesData: FaqItem[] = [
    {
        question: 'UI/UX Design',
        answer: `Elevate your digital presence with our bespoke UI/UX designs, where functionality meets beauty, ensuring your users enjoy every interaction.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Prototyping',
        answer: `Bring your ideas to life with rapid prototyping, testing the waters before diving deep, ensuring your product hits the mark right from the start.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'React',
        answer: `Build fast, responsive web applications with React, creating seamless user experiences with a modern JavaScript library.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Next.js',
        answer: `Leverage Next.js for your projects to benefit from server-side rendering and static site generation, boosting speed and SEO performance.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Vue.js',
        answer: `Opt for Vue.js to create engaging, high-performance web interfaces that are both powerful and easy to maintain.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Tailwind',
        answer: `Streamline your development process with Tailwind CSS, crafting custom designs with speed and efficiency without sacrificing creativity.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'TypeScript',
        answer: `Improve your project's stability and maintainability with TypeScript, enhancing JavaScript with static types for safer, more predictable code.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Node.js',
        answer: `Develop scalable, high-performance backend solutions with Node.js, enabling real-time data processing and application performance.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Ruby',
        answer: `Embrace the elegance and simplicity of Ruby for building dynamic, database-backed web applications with clean, readable code.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Rails',
        answer: `Accelerate your web development with Rails, a powerful framework that emphasizes convention over configuration for rapid development cycles.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'PostgreSQL',
        answer: `Store and manage your data with PostgreSQL, the advanced, open-source relational database known for its reliability and flexibility.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Analytics',
        answer: `Craft a unique brand identity that resonates with your audience, setting you apart in a crowded marketplace with a memorable visual story.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Research',
        answer: `Elevate your project's foundation with our comprehensive Research services, delving deep to uncover market trends, user needs, and innovative opportunities for growth.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Project Management',
        answer: `Navigate your project's journey with our expert management, ensuring seamless progression from blueprint to final delivery.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Presenting',
        answer: `Transform your ideas into compelling narratives with our presentation design services, captivating your audience and leaving a lasting impression.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Web Design',
        answer: `Create stunning, user-friendly websites with our design team, ensuring your site reflects your brand perfectly and enhances user experience.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Motion Design',
        answer: `Add a layer of engagement with motion design, bringing static visuals to life and keeping your audience glued to the screen.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Animation & Interaction',
        answer: `Immerse users in your digital world with custom animations and interactive elements that elevate the user experience to new heights.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Spline',
        answer: `Utilize the latest in 3D web design with Spline, crafting immersive experiences that dazzle and engage your audience like never before.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Webflow Design & Development',
        answer: `Harness the power of Webflow with our expertise, building responsive, dynamic websites that are both beautiful and easy to manage.`,
    },
]
